psupedia.info 2009-06-17

# Privacy Policy - The PSUPedia

**The wiki is currently being migrated and may be subject to unforeseen downtime. Please use[this](http://ambitionofilluminus.com/Main_Page "http://ambitionofilluminus.com/Main_Page") if the main wiki is inaccessible.**  
**Please note that the rule on multiple user page edits is still being enforced.**

### From The PSUPedia

Privacy Policy (Redirected from The PSUPedia:Privacy policy)

## Contents

  * 1 Ground Rules
  * 2 Information Collection and Use
  * 3 Cookies
  * 4 Sharing
  * 5 Links
  * 6 Surveys & Contests
  * 7 Security
  * 8 Notification of Changes

##  Ground Rules 

  * We will tell you: 
    * What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the web site. 
    * The organization collecting the information. 
    * How the information is used. 
    * With whom the information may be shared. 
    * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information. 
    * The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under PSUPedia control. 
    * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information 

##  Information Collection and Use 

PSUPedia is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. 

##  Cookies 

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to participate in any of our Sweepstakes, Contests or monthly Drawings that take place. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

##  Sharing 

We won't share any demographic or personal information obtained by registration at PSUPedia. 

##  Links 

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we PSUPedia are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

##  Surveys & Contests 

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (e-mail address, and usernames.). 

##  Security 

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both on-line and off-line. 

##  Notification of Changes 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
